Recharts. No one top is in, no one bottom
is in. So many different strategies,
right? But for this sake of protecting our
money, the least risky way of investing,
and the one you can start off with $10,
$20, $30, right, is DCA, dollar cost
average. And this method is great because
not only can you diversify your portfolio
with this method, you can compound on it.
So what I like about DCA-ing is, let's say
for the rest of this year, you know, you
put in $25 a week into a company or into
stocks or whatever the case may be. That
$25 a week will compound as the months,
the weeks go, right? So some people will
take a whole thousand dollars and put it
in one, you know, company. You can dollar
cost average, meaning you're getting in
where you are at. So if the stock is $70
and you put in $25 in, you're getting in
at $70. If it rises to $80 and you keep
doing it, now you're getting in at $80,
right? But we always want to get at it at
a lower price so that way as our compounds
or the stock grow, so does our compounding
deposits, right? So for seven days, you
can do 25 day one, 25 day two, 25 day
three. And on the next week, that which
you have invested in that week would
should compound into how your gains and
how your returns. So you keep doing that
for a month, then you look back 30 days
and you like, wow, that was just from $25
a week. So I just wanted to give that, you
know, strategy because, you know, I don't
have, you know, the play to watch the
chart go from here to the top. And when it
comes back, when I pull back and take it
back up, I don't have that for you. I
wouldn't suggest it if you're not a
serious trader. So if you're not a serious
trader, you've got some extra funds and
you just want to put it in the stock
market and let it sit and let it ride.
Dollar cost averaging would be your best
strategy. Again, it's safe, simple, and
you can start off with a little as $10,
right? And if you need to get into
Robinhood, I will place my referral down
in the description where you and I can
both earn and get a piece of a stock for
free just for signing up. So yeah, if you
don't want to put in your funds yet, but
you still want a piece of a stock, you
know, to feel like an investor and be a
part of the stock market, you know, check
out my referral link on Robinhood and
let's get us some free stocks and let's
keep investing. All right.
All right, y'all, what's going on? So I
just want to say thank you for reaching to
this point in the video. This video is a
long video. And if you made it to this end
to watching it, that means you've seen all
the stuff I discussed, you know,
tokenization, DCA, and pretty much getting
ready for this bull run. It's about to
happen and how to prepare for it, how to
not lose your money, you know, invest in
small, invest in what you can, and having
the terminology and awareness of what's
happening, right? So if you made it to
this end, to the market watch list, to the
list that I invested in, over 25 stocks
that I am looking at, and, you know, over
five different areas of the sector of
stocks and crypto, you know, you have
shown that you are ready and you want to
do this, right? And by that, I mean you
have invested not only just your money for
purchasing this video, you have invested
your time in learning, right? So shout out
to you, the viewer, the receiver, the
investor for, you know, preparing for your
future. All right. Again, as I promised
you guys, you know,